<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Recruityard</title>
        <link>https://www.recruityard.com</link>
        <description>Recruityard - Current Job Openings</description>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Icelandic - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-icelandic-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Icelandic and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Portugal - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Icelandic.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apoio ao Cliente com Francês - Remoto]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/apoio-ao-cliente-com-frances-remoto-em-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Local de trabalho: Portugal</p>
<p>É fluente em Francês e tem fortes competências de comunicação? Temos oportunidades de emprego entusiasmantes em Portugal! Dê o próximo passo na sua carreira ao trabalhar com algumas das principais marcas globais.</p>
<h3>O que irá fazer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comunicar com clientes por telefone, chat e email;</li>
<li>- Monitorizar e resolver casos de forma eficiente, garantindo uma rápida resolução;</li>
<li>- Assegurar a satisfação dos clientes, representando uma marca de prestígio;</li>
<li>- Desenvolver e manter relações sólidas e profissionais com parceiros, demonstrando sempre empatia;</li>
<li>- Trabalhar para alcançar os objetivos definidos pelo cliente e pela empresa.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que procuramos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluência em Francês;</li>
<li>- Fortes capacidades de comunicação, relacionamento interpessoal e resolução de problemas;</li>
<li>- Conhecimentos básicos de informática e competências técnicas;</li>
<li>- Capacidade de multitarefa;</li>
<li>- Espírito de equipa e capacidade de prosperar num ambiente dinâmico e enérgico.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que oferecemos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- 40h semanais</li>
<li>- Salário mensal competitivo;</li>
<li>- Benefícios de saúde e vários outros descontos;</li>
<li>- Formação completa ministrada por formadores certificados;</li>
<li>- Oportunidades de progressão na carreira e desenvolvimento profissional;</li>
<li>- Local de trabalho - Portugal</li>
</ul>
<p>Está a dar o seu consentimento, ao abrigo do RGPD, para que os detalhes do seu CV sejam partilhados diretamente com o nosso cliente para fins de recrutamento.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Russian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-russian-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Russian and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Russian-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Russian; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with French]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-french-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in French?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in French.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apoio ao Cliente com Francês]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/apoio-ao-cliente-com-frances-em-braga-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Local de trabalho: Braga</p>
<p>É fluente em Francês e tem fortes competências de comunicação? Temos oportunidades de emprego entusiasmantes em Braga! Dê o próximo passo na sua carreira ao trabalhar com algumas das principais marcas globais.</p>
<h3>O que irá fazer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comunicar com clientes por telefone, chat e email;</li>
<li>- Monitorizar e resolver casos de forma eficiente, garantindo uma rápida resolução;</li>
<li>- Assegurar a satisfação dos clientes, representando uma marca de prestígio;</li>
<li>- Desenvolver e manter relações sólidas e profissionais com parceiros, demonstrando sempre empatia;</li>
<li>- Trabalhar para alcançar os objetivos definidos pelo cliente e pela empresa.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que procuramos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluência em Francês;</li>
<li>- Fortes capacidades de comunicação, relacionamento interpessoal e resolução de problemas;</li>
<li>- Conhecimentos básicos de informática e competências técnicas;</li>
<li>- Capacidade de multitarefa;</li>
<li>- Espírito de equipa e capacidade de prosperar num ambiente dinâmico e enérgico.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que oferecemos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- 40h semanais</li>
<li>- Salário mensal competitivo;</li>
<li>- Benefícios de saúde e vários outros descontos;</li>
<li>- Formação completa ministrada por formadores certificados;</li>
<li>- Oportunidades de progressão na carreira e desenvolvimento profissional;</li>
<li>- Local de trabalho - Braga</li>
</ul>
<p>Está a dar o seu consentimento, ao abrigo do RGPD, para que os detalhes do seu CV sejam partilhados diretamente com o nosso cliente para fins de recrutamento.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support with Slovenian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-with-slovenian-in-sofia-bg]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>Are you passionate about customer service? This is your opportunity! We are looking for talented and enthusiastic individuals to join our client in Sofia!</p>
<p>We are interested in candidates who speak Slovenian and with an extensive Customer Service experience. If you want to work in a dynamic and multicultural environment, we want to meet you!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Slovenian;</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills;</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Sofia for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Czech]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-czech-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Czech and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Czech-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Czech; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Service Agent - Banking Company with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-service-agent-banking-company-with-german-in-szczecin-pl]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in German and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Szczecin! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>Your Mission:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide customer service support and resolve routine issues related to banking products and services.</li>
<li>- Help customers with their financial challenges and find quick, efficient solutions.</li>
<li>- Deliver top-quality service and build positive customer experiences.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with your team to make each day a success.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We’re Looking For:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- German speaker – B2+/C1 level</li>
<li>- Strong communication and problem-solving skills.</li>
<li>- Passion for teamwork and learning.</li>
<li>- Customer-oriented mindset, especially in the financial sector.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Salary: 7,500 PLN gross/month.</li>
<li>- Contract Type: Labour contract (UoP) – stable and fully protected by Polish Labour Law.</li>
<li>- Benefits: LuxMed, MultiSport, MyBenefit cafeteria, and more!</li>
<li>- Working Hours: Full-time, shifts between 07:00 – 22:00, Monday to Sunday (365 days).</li>
<li>- Work Model: Onsite in Szczecin, Poland with a hybrid option (1 week in the office, 3 weeks from home) possible after 3-6 months of adaptation.</li>
<li>- Growth opportunities in the banking industry with top-tier training provided.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Norwegian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-norwegian-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Norwegian and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Norwegian-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Norwegian; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales Advisor with Czech]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/sales-advisor-with-czech-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>As a Sales Advisor, you will identify and cultivate new business opportunities, consult with clients to understand their needs, and provide tailored solutions to drive growth while achieving sales targets.</p>
<h3>Your responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Daily communication with new and existing clients (agencies or advertisers) via phone, chat, and email to identify sales opportunities and offer solutions tailored to their business goals.</li>
<li>- Consultative selling to better understand clients' needs and help them achieve their objectives.</li>
<li>- Planning actions based on clients needs and expectations.</li>
<li>- Researching industries and business models to better understand markets and clients.</li>
<li>- Understanding local specifics to better tailor offers for local advertisers.</li>
<li>- Providing personalized recommendations based on clients needs.</li>
<li>- Assisting clients in optimizing product usage, offering active support in problem-solving and performance improvement.</li>
<li>- Expanding knowledge of advertising solutions and their impact on business performance.</li>
<li>- Solving problems, identifying trends, and providing valuable feedback on products.</li>
<li>- Using various tools to communicate effectively and help clients succeed.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Employer requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Czech.</li>
<li>- Communicative English (at least B2 level).</li>
<li>- Previous experience in sales and/or marketing is preferred.</li>
<li>- Strong verbal and written communication skills.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Opportunity to advance your career within an international and multicultural environment.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance coverage from your first day.</li>
<li>- Extensive training, plus dedicated coaches to support personal and professional growth.</li>
<li>- A clear path for growth and development within the organization, with support from a highly collaborative team.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with French]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-french-in-porto-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in French and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the French-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in French; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Czech - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-czech-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Czech and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Czech.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apoio ao Cliente com Francês]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/apoio-ao-cliente-com-frances-in-braga-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Local de trabalho: Guimarães</p>
<p>É fluente em Francês e tem fortes competências de comunicação? Temos oportunidades de emprego entusiasmantes em Guimarães! Dê o próximo passo na sua carreira ao trabalhar com algumas das principais marcas globais.</p>
<h3>O que irá fazer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comunicar com clientes por telefone, chat e email;</li>
<li>- Monitorizar e resolver casos de forma eficiente, garantindo uma rápida resolução;</li>
<li>- Assegurar a satisfação dos clientes, representando uma marca de prestígio;</li>
<li>- Desenvolver e manter relações sólidas e profissionais com parceiros, demonstrando sempre empatia;</li>
<li>- Trabalhar para alcançar os objetivos definidos pelo cliente e pela empresa.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que procuramos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluência em Francês;</li>
<li>- Fortes capacidades de comunicação, relacionamento interpessoal e resolução de problemas;</li>
<li>- Conhecimentos básicos de informática e competências técnicas;</li>
<li>- Capacidade de multitarefa;</li>
<li>- Espírito de equipa e capacidade de prosperar num ambiente dinâmico e enérgico.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que oferecemos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- 40h semanais</li>
<li>- Salário mensal competitivo;</li>
<li>- Benefícios de saúde e vários outros descontos;</li>
<li>- Formação completa ministrada por formadores certificados;</li>
<li>- Oportunidades de progressão na carreira e desenvolvimento profissional;</li>
<li>- Local de trabalho - Guimarães</li>
</ul>
<p>Está a dar o seu consentimento, ao abrigo do RGPD, para que os detalhes do seu CV sejam partilhados diretamente com o nosso cliente para fins de recrutamento.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support with French - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-with-french-remote-in-bulgaria-bg]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>Are you passionate about customer service? This is your opportunity! We are looking for talented and enthusiastic individuals to join our client in Bulgaria!</p>
<p>We are interested in candidates who speak French and with an extensive Customer Service experience. If you want to work in a dynamic and multicultural environment, we want to meet you!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in French;</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills;</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Bulgaria for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Hungarian - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-hungarian-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Hungarian and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Hungarian.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with Dutch]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-dutch-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in Dutch?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Dutch.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with Arabic]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-arabic-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in Arabic?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Arabic.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Consultant – Retention (German Speaking) - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-consultant-retention-(german-speaking)-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Location: Remote in Portugal</p>
<p>Workload: 100% (Full-Time, Permanent Contract)</p>
<h3>Position Overview:</h3>
<p>We are looking for German-speaking Customer Consultants to join the Retention team. Your main responsibility will be handling incoming calls from customers intending to cancel their contracts, aiming to retain them through excellent service, upselling, and cross-selling where applicable.</p>
<h3>Main Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Manage inbound customer calls regarding contract cancellations.</li>
<li>- Advise customers on services and offers to maintain or increase their subscription value.</li>
<li>- Upsell and cross-sell products and services.</li>
<li>- Ensure a high level of customer satisfaction and loyalty.</li>
<li>- Meet defined quality and performance standards.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Candidate Profile:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluent in German (mandatory) and good command of English.</li>
<li>- Previous experience in a call center is valued but not mandatory.</li>
<li>- Strong customer service and communication skills.</li>
<li>- Resilience, flexibility, and ability to work under pressure.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented, reliable, and punctual.</li>
<li>- Basic PC skills.</li>
<li>- Completed technical training or equivalent professional experience.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Work Schedule:</h3>
<h3>Monday to Friday, rotating shifts:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- 07:00 – 16:00</li>
<li>- 08:00 – 17:00</li>
<li>- 09:00 – 18:00</li>
</ul>
<h3>Compensation & Benefits Package:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Basic Salary: EUR 900.00 gross/month</li>
<li>- Performance Bonus (up to): EUR 360.00/month</li>
<li>- Language Allowance (German + English): EUR 500.00/month</li>
<li>- Meal Allowance of EUR 9.60 per day worked - up to EUR 201.60/month</li>
<li>- Assiduity Allowance: EUR 110.00/month</li>
<li>- Flex Work Allowance: EUR 60.00/month</li>
</ul>
<p>Why Apply?</p>
<p>Permanent, stable employment within a leading company in the telecommunications sector.</p>
<p>Real opportunities for professional development and career growth.</p>
<p>Multicultural and dynamic work environment.</p>
<p>Attractive compensation package including fixed and variable components.</p>
<p>Work fully remote in Portugal</p>
<p>If this opportunity matches your profile, we would be happy to receive your application!</p>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with Turkish]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-turkish-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in Turkish?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Turkish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Finnish - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-finnish-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Finnish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Finnish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interpreter with Russian - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/interpreter-with-russian-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Remote work - Equipment provided by the company. We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. As an Interpreter with Russian, you will be responsible for delivering accurate and confidential interpretation services across various fields. This role demands strong linguistic skills, cultural awareness, and the ability to convey information with clarity and precision. This position may involve both remote and on-site assignments, depending on project requirements.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide accurate and effective interpretation in real-time, ensuring clarity and understanding across languages.</li>
<li>- Perform interpretation through various channels, such as phone, video, and in-person meetings, adapting to the needs of each situation.</li>
<li>- Maintain confidentiality and sensitivity to diverse cultural nuances in all interpreted conversations.</li>
<li>- Work independently while following ethical standards and protocols specific to each industry or client.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Qualifications:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Russian and English is required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in professional interpretation, especially within sectors such as healthcare, legal, or business, is preferred.</li>
<li>- Familiarity with remote interpretation platforms and digital communication tools.</li>
<li>- Strong verbal communication skills, with the ability to remain neutral and impartial in all interpretations.</li>
<li>- Availability for various shifts, including nights, weekends, and holidays as needed, based on client requirements.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Training and Development:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive training program covering interpretation protocols, software, and industry-specific terminology.</li>
<li>- Ongoing professional development to enhance language skills, cultural competence, and industry knowledge.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits and Compensation:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Competitive compensation package, with options for healthcare benefits, holiday pay, and other allowances based on location and assignment type.</li>
<li>- For remote interpreters, we provide essential technical equipment as required (e.g., headset, computer, secure connection).</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Hebrew]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-hebrew-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Hebrew and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Hebrew-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Hebrew; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Polish - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-polish-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Polish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Polish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interpreter with Ukrainian - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/interpreter-with-ukrainian-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Remote work - Equipment provided by the company. We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. As an Interpreter with Ukrainian, you will be responsible for delivering accurate and confidential interpretation services across various fields. This role demands strong linguistic skills, cultural awareness, and the ability to convey information with clarity and precision. This position may involve both remote and on-site assignments, depending on project requirements.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide accurate and effective interpretation in real-time, ensuring clarity and understanding across languages.</li>
<li>- Perform interpretation through various channels, such as phone, video, and in-person meetings, adapting to the needs of each situation.</li>
<li>- Maintain confidentiality and sensitivity to diverse cultural nuances in all interpreted conversations.</li>
<li>- Work independently while following ethical standards and protocols specific to each industry or client.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Qualifications:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Ukrainian and English is required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in professional interpretation, especially within sectors such as healthcare, legal, or business, is preferred.</li>
<li>- Familiarity with remote interpretation platforms and digital communication tools.</li>
<li>- Strong verbal communication skills, with the ability to remain neutral and impartial in all interpretations.</li>
<li>- Availability for various shifts, including nights, weekends, and holidays as needed, based on client requirements.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Training and Development:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive training program covering interpretation protocols, software, and industry-specific terminology.</li>
<li>- Ongoing professional development to enhance language skills, cultural competence, and industry knowledge.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits and Compensation:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Competitive compensation package, with options for healthcare benefits, holiday pay, and other allowances based on location and assignment type.</li>
<li>- For remote interpreters, we provide essential technical equipment as required (e.g., headset, computer, secure connection).</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Italian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-italian-in-porto-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Italian and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Italian-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Italian; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-with-german-in-sofia-bg]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>Are you passionate about customer service? This is your opportunity! We are looking for talented and enthusiastic individuals to join our client in Sofia!</p>
<p>We are interested in candidates who speak German and with an extensive Customer Service experience. If you want to work in a dynamic and multicultural environment, we want to meet you!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in German;</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills;</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Sofia for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with Italian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-italian-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in Italian?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Italian.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Portuguese - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-portuguese-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Portuguese and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Portuguese.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Icelandic - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-icelandic-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Icelandic and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Icelandic.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apoio ao Cliente com Francês]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/apoio-ao-cliente-com-frances-in-porto-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Local de trabalho: Porto</p>
<p>É fluente em Francês e tem fortes competências de comunicação? Temos oportunidades de emprego entusiasmantes em Porto! Dê o próximo passo na sua carreira ao trabalhar com algumas das principais marcas globais.</p>
<h3>O que irá fazer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comunicar com clientes por telefone, chat e email;</li>
<li>- Monitorizar e resolver casos de forma eficiente, garantindo uma rápida resolução;</li>
<li>- Assegurar a satisfação dos clientes, representando uma marca de prestígio;</li>
<li>- Desenvolver e manter relações sólidas e profissionais com parceiros, demonstrando sempre empatia;</li>
<li>- Trabalhar para alcançar os objetivos definidos pelo cliente e pela empresa.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que procuramos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluência em Francês;</li>
<li>- Fortes capacidades de comunicação, relacionamento interpessoal e resolução de problemas;</li>
<li>- Conhecimentos básicos de informática e competências técnicas;</li>
<li>- Capacidade de multitarefa;</li>
<li>- Espírito de equipa e capacidade de prosperar num ambiente dinâmico e enérgico.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que oferecemos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- 40h semanais</li>
<li>- Salário mensal competitivo;</li>
<li>- Benefícios de saúde e vários outros descontos;</li>
<li>- Formação completa ministrada por formadores certificados;</li>
<li>- Oportunidades de progressão na carreira e desenvolvimento profissional;</li>
<li>- Local de trabalho - Porto</li>
</ul>
<p>Está a dar o seu consentimento, ao abrigo do RGPD, para que os detalhes do seu CV sejam partilhados diretamente com o nosso cliente para fins de recrutamento.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support with Dutch]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-with-dutch-in-sofia-bg]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>Are you passionate about customer service? This is your opportunity! We are looking for talented and enthusiastic individuals to join our client in Sofia!</p>
<p>We are interested in candidates who speak Dutch and with an extensive Customer Service experience. If you want to work in a dynamic and multicultural environment, we want to meet you!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Dutch;</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills;</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Sofia for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beauty Advisor with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/beauty-advisor-with-german-in-porto-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Porto!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team.</p>
<p>We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential.</p>
<p>Are you fluent in German and passionate about beauty? Represent a luxury brand in Customer Care – this opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide advice, answer questions, and promote the client’s brands in every interaction;</li>
<li>- Communicate with consumers by telephone, email, live chat, messaging and social media;</li>
<li>- Provide advanced sales through servicing to ensure well rounded and complete beauty solution for consumers;</li>
<li>- Place orders, resolve technical queries, and undertake associated administrative activities.</li>
<li>- Provide first contact resolution on service inquiries, complaints and on complex consumer questions within a variety of topics;</li>
<li>- Liaise with leadership and other teams to ensure a full resolution for the consumer.</li>
<li>- Understand the potential risk to the business of some inquiries/complaints; Show awareness when cases need to be escalated to an I&E advisor or Team Leader (i.e. viral social media public posts)</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluent level of written and verbal communication skills in German.</li>
<li>- Good level of written and verbal communication skills in English (minimum B2).</li>
<li>- Excellent communication skills and social intelligence – empathy, self-awareness, cultural sensitivity.</li>
<li>- Aptitude for problem-solving;</li>
<li>- Dynamism and team spirit;</li>
<li>- Flexible and quick learner, able to adapt continuously.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Porto for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Danish - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-danish-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Danish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Portugal - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Danish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Dutch]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-dutch-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Dutch and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Dutch-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Dutch; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-german-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in German and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the German-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in German; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Bulgarian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-bulgarian-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Bulgarian and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Bulgarian-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Bulgarian; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Norwegian - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-norwegian-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Norwegian and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Portugal - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Norwegian.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support with Slovak]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-with-slovak-in-sofia-bg]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>Are you passionate about customer service? This is your opportunity! We are looking for talented and enthusiastic individuals to join our client in Sofia!</p>
<p>We are interested in candidates who speak Slovak and with an extensive Customer Service experience. If you want to work in a dynamic and multicultural environment, we want to meet you!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Slovak;</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills;</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Sofia for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Finnish - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-finnish-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Finnish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Portugal - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Finnish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Norwegian - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-norwegian-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Norwegian and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Norwegian.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Italian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-italian-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Italian and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Italian-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Italian; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with Czech]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-czech-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in Czech?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Czech.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with Greek]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-greek-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in Greek?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Greek.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with German - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-german-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in German and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Portugal - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in German.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales Advisor with French - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/sales-advisor-with-french-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>As a Sales Advisor, you will identify and cultivate new business opportunities, consult with clients to understand their needs, and provide tailored solutions to drive growth while achieving sales targets.</p>
<h3>Your responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Daily communication with new and existing clients (agencies or advertisers) via phone, chat, and email to identify sales opportunities and offer solutions tailored to their business goals.</li>
<li>- Consultative selling to better understand clients' needs and help them achieve their objectives.</li>
<li>- Planning actions based on clients needs and expectations.</li>
<li>- Researching industries and business models to better understand markets and clients.</li>
<li>- Understanding local specifics to better tailor offers for local advertisers.</li>
<li>- Providing personalized recommendations based on clients needs.</li>
<li>- Assisting clients in optimizing product usage, offering active support in problem-solving and performance improvement.</li>
<li>- Expanding knowledge of advertising solutions and their impact on business performance.</li>
<li>- Solving problems, identifying trends, and providing valuable feedback on products.</li>
<li>- Using various tools to communicate effectively and help clients succeed.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Employer requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in French.</li>
<li>- Communicative English (at least B2 level).</li>
<li>- Previous experience in sales and/or marketing is mandatory.</li>
<li>- Strong verbal and written communication skills.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Opportunity to advance your career within an international and multicultural environment.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance coverage from your first day.</li>
<li>- Extensive training, plus dedicated coaches to support personal and professional growth.</li>
<li>- A clear path for growth and development within the organization, with support from a highly collaborative team.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with French]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-french-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in French and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the French-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in French; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-with-german-in-pomeranian-voivodeship-pl-2]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>Are you passionate about customer service? This is your opportunity! We are looking for talented and enthusiastic individuals to join our client in Gdansk!</p>
<p>We are interested in candidates who speak German and with an extensive Customer Service experience. If you want to work in a dynamic and multicultural environment, we want to meet you!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in German;</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills;</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Gdansk for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with Hebrew]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-hebrew-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in Hebrew?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Hebrew.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Services Officer with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-services-officer-with-german-in-madrid-es]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Our client  is currently seeking new Client Services Officer on a permanent contract to join them and help meet the challenges of our growth.</p>
<p>This position is based at our Madrid office, where you will become part of a dynamic and supportive management team.</p>
<p>In this role, you will advise and assist our clients with their inquiries via phone and email.</p>
<p>Are you fluent in German and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Madrid! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Handle customer inquiries and provide advice regarding their health insurance contracts, coverage, reimbursements, and all aspects of their contract life (subscription, amendments, cancellations, premiums, etc.).</li>
<li>- Contracts: registration and cancellation, premium collection.</li>
<li>- Health services: enter reimbursements, create quotes, issue coverage approvals... in accordance with internal procedures.</li>
<li>- Client files: update and modify customer records (contract details, address, bank account information, etc.).</li>
<li>- Contribute to customer satisfaction through the quality of your responses, the efficiency of your work, and your contribution to achieving performance indicators.</li>
<li>- There will be no sales or prospecting involved in this role.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in German</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Permanent contract</li>
<li>- Free healthcare insurance for you and your family</li>
<li>- Annual variable bonus if you achieve your objectives, quarterly bonus & annual bonus depending on the results of the company and medical teleconsultation.</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Italian - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-italian-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Italian and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Italian.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with German - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-german-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in German and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in German.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Services Officer with English]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-services-officer-with-english-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Our client  is currently seeking new Client Services Officer on a permanent contract to join them and help meet the challenges of our growth.</p>
<p>This position is based at our Lisbon office, where you will become part of a dynamic and supportive management team.</p>
<p>In this role, you will advise and assist our clients with their inquiries via phone and email.</p>
<p>Are you fluent in English and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Handle customer inquiries and provide advice regarding their health insurance contracts, coverage, reimbursements, and all aspects of their contract life (subscription, amendments, cancellations, premiums, etc.).</li>
<li>- Contracts: registration and cancellation, premium collection.</li>
<li>- Health services: enter reimbursements, create quotes, issue coverage approvals... in accordance with internal procedures.</li>
<li>- Client files: update and modify customer records (contract details, address, bank account information, etc.).</li>
<li>- Contribute to customer satisfaction through the quality of your responses, the efficiency of your work, and your contribution to achieving performance indicators.</li>
<li>- There will be no sales or prospecting involved in this role.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in English</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Permanent contract</li>
<li>- Free healthcare insurance for you and your family</li>
<li>- Annual variable bonus if you achieve your objectives, quaterly bonus & annual bonus depending on the results of the company and medical teleconsultation.</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales Advisor with Estonian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/sales-advisor-with-estonian-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>As a Sales Advisor, you will identify and cultivate new business opportunities, consult with clients to understand their needs, and provide tailored solutions to drive growth while achieving sales targets.</p>
<h3>Your responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Daily communication with new and existing clients (agencies or advertisers) via phone, chat, and email to identify sales opportunities and offer solutions tailored to their business goals.</li>
<li>- Consultative selling to better understand clients' needs and help them achieve their objectives.</li>
<li>- Planning actions based on clients needs and expectations.</li>
<li>- Researching industries and business models to better understand markets and clients.</li>
<li>- Understanding local specifics to better tailor offers for local advertisers.</li>
<li>- Providing personalized recommendations based on clients needs.</li>
<li>- Assisting clients in optimizing product usage, offering active support in problem-solving and performance improvement.</li>
<li>- Expanding knowledge of advertising solutions and their impact on business performance.</li>
<li>- Solving problems, identifying trends, and providing valuable feedback on products.</li>
<li>- Using various tools to communicate effectively and help clients succeed.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Employer requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Estonian.</li>
<li>- Communicative English (at least B2 level).</li>
<li>- Previous experience in sales and/or marketing is preferred.</li>
<li>- Strong verbal and written communication skills.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to  for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Opportunity to advance your career within an international and multicultural environment.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance coverage from your first day.</li>
<li>- Extensive training, plus dedicated coaches to support personal and professional growth.</li>
<li>- A clear path for growth and development within the organization, with support from a highly collaborative team.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Swedish - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-swedish-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Swedish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Swedish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apoio ao Cliente com Alemão]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/apoio-ao-cliente-com-alemao-em-braga-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Local de trabalho: Braga</p>
<p>É fluente em Alemão e tem fortes competências de comunicação? Temos oportunidades de emprego entusiasmantes em Braga! Dê o próximo passo na sua carreira ao trabalhar com algumas das principais marcas globais.</p>
<h3>O que irá fazer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comunicar com clientes por telefone, chat e email;</li>
<li>- Monitorizar e resolver casos de forma eficiente, garantindo uma rápida resolução;</li>
<li>- Assegurar a satisfação dos clientes, representando uma marca de prestígio;</li>
<li>- Desenvolver e manter relações sólidas e profissionais com parceiros, demonstrando sempre empatia;</li>
<li>- Trabalhar para alcançar os objetivos definidos pelo cliente e pela empresa.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que procuramos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluência em Alemão;</li>
<li>- Fortes capacidades de comunicação, relacionamento interpessoal e resolução de problemas;</li>
<li>- Conhecimentos básicos de informática e competências técnicas;</li>
<li>- Capacidade de multitarefa;</li>
<li>- Espírito de equipa e capacidade de prosperar num ambiente dinâmico e enérgico.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que oferecemos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- 40h semanais</li>
<li>- Salário mensal competitivo;</li>
<li>- Benefícios de saúde e vários outros descontos;</li>
<li>- Formação completa ministrada por formadores certificados;</li>
<li>- Oportunidades de progressão na carreira e desenvolvimento profissional;</li>
<li>- Local de trabalho - Braga</li>
</ul>
<p>Está a dar o seu consentimento, ao abrigo do RGPD, para que os detalhes do seu CV sejam partilhados diretamente com o nosso cliente para fins de recrutamento.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Finnish]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-finnish-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Finnish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Finnish-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Finnish; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support with Czech]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-with-czech-in-sofia-bg]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>Are you passionate about customer service? This is your opportunity! We are looking for talented and enthusiastic individuals to join our client in Sofia!</p>
<p>We are interested in candidates who speak Czech and with an extensive Customer Service experience. If you want to work in a dynamic and multicultural environment, we want to meet you!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Czech;</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills;</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Sofia for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Swedish - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-swedish-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Swedish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Portugal - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Swedish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Dutch - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-dutch-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Dutch and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Dutch.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with English]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-english-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in English?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in English.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Danish - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-danish-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Danish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Danish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales Advisor with Polish]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/sales-advisor-with-polish-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>As a Sales Advisor, you will identify and cultivate new business opportunities, consult with clients to understand their needs, and provide tailored solutions to drive growth while achieving sales targets.</p>
<h3>Your responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Daily communication with new and existing clients (agencies or advertisers) via phone, chat, and email to identify sales opportunities and offer solutions tailored to their business goals.</li>
<li>- Consultative selling to better understand clients' needs and help them achieve their objectives.</li>
<li>- Planning actions based on clients needs and expectations.</li>
<li>- Researching industries and business models to better understand markets and clients.</li>
<li>- Understanding local specifics to better tailor offers for local advertisers.</li>
<li>- Providing personalized recommendations based on clients needs.</li>
<li>- Assisting clients in optimizing product usage, offering active support in problem-solving and performance improvement.</li>
<li>- Expanding knowledge of advertising solutions and their impact on business performance.</li>
<li>- Solving problems, identifying trends, and providing valuable feedback on products.</li>
<li>- Using various tools to communicate effectively and help clients succeed.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Employer requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Polish.</li>
<li>- Communicative English (at least B2 level).</li>
<li>- Previous experience in sales and/or marketing is preferred.</li>
<li>- Strong verbal and written communication skills.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to  for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Opportunity to advance your career within an international and multicultural environment.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance coverage from your first day.</li>
<li>- Extensive training, plus dedicated coaches to support personal and professional growth.</li>
<li>- A clear path for growth and development within the organization, with support from a highly collaborative team.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beauty Advisor with Dutch]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/beauty-advisor-with-dutch-in-porto-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Porto!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team.</p>
<p>We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential.</p>
<p>Are you fluent in Dutch and passionate about beauty? Represent a luxury brand in Customer Care – this opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide advice, answer questions, and promote the client’s brands in every interaction;</li>
<li>- Communicate with consumers by telephone, email, live chat, messaging and social media;</li>
<li>- Provide advanced sales through servicing to ensure well rounded and complete beauty solution for consumers;</li>
<li>- Place orders, resolve technical queries, and undertake associated administrative activities.</li>
<li>- Provide first contact resolution on service inquiries, complaints and on complex consumer questions within a variety of topics;</li>
<li>- Liaise with leadership and other teams to ensure a full resolution for the consumer.</li>
<li>- Understand the potential risk to the business of some inquiries/complaints; Show awareness when cases need to be escalated to an I&E advisor or Team Leader (i.e. viral social media public posts)</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluent level of written and verbal communication skills in Dutch.</li>
<li>- Good level of written and verbal communication skills in English (minimum B2).</li>
<li>- Excellent communication skills and social intelligence – empathy, self-awareness, cultural sensitivity.</li>
<li>- Aptitude for problem-solving;</li>
<li>- Dynamism and team spirit;</li>
<li>- Flexible and quick learner, able to adapt continuously.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Porto for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales Advisor with Lithuanian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/sales-advisor-with-lithuanian-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>As a Sales Advisor, you will identify and cultivate new business opportunities, consult with clients to understand their needs, and provide tailored solutions to drive growth while achieving sales targets.</p>
<h3>Your responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Daily communication with new and existing clients (agencies or advertisers) via phone, chat, and email to identify sales opportunities and offer solutions tailored to their business goals.</li>
<li>- Consultative selling to better understand clients' needs and help them achieve their objectives.</li>
<li>- Planning actions based on clients needs and expectations.</li>
<li>- Researching industries and business models to better understand markets and clients.</li>
<li>- Understanding local specifics to better tailor offers for local advertisers.</li>
<li>- Providing personalized recommendations based on clients needs.</li>
<li>- Assisting clients in optimizing product usage, offering active support in problem-solving and performance improvement.</li>
<li>- Expanding knowledge of advertising solutions and their impact on business performance.</li>
<li>- Solving problems, identifying trends, and providing valuable feedback on products.</li>
<li>- Using various tools to communicate effectively and help clients succeed.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Employer requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Lithuanian.</li>
<li>- Communicative English (at least B2 level).</li>
<li>- Previous experience in sales and/or marketing is preferred.</li>
<li>- Strong verbal and written communication skills.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to  for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Opportunity to advance your career within an international and multicultural environment.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance coverage from your first day.</li>
<li>- Extensive training, plus dedicated coaches to support personal and professional growth.</li>
<li>- A clear path for growth and development within the organization, with support from a highly collaborative team.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Ukrainian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-ukrainian-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Ukrainian and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Ukrainian-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Ukrainian; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Swedish]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-swedish-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Swedish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Swedish-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Swedish; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Services Officer with English]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-services-officer-with-english-in-madrid-es]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Our client  is currently seeking new Client Services Officer on a permanent contract to join them and help meet the challenges of our growth.</p>
<p>This position is based at our Madrid office, where you will become part of a dynamic and supportive management team.</p>
<p>In this role, you will advise and assist our clients with their inquiries via phone and email.</p>
<p>Are you fluent in English and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Madrid! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Handle customer inquiries and provide advice regarding their health insurance contracts, coverage, reimbursements, and all aspects of their contract life (subscription, amendments, cancellations, premiums, etc.).</li>
<li>- Contracts: registration and cancellation, premium collection.</li>
<li>- Health services: enter reimbursements, create quotes, issue coverage approvals... in accordance with internal procedures.</li>
<li>- Client files: update and modify customer records (contract details, address, bank account information, etc.).</li>
<li>- Contribute to customer satisfaction through the quality of your responses, the efficiency of your work, and your contribution to achieving performance indicators.</li>
<li>- There will be no sales or prospecting involved in this role.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in English</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Permanent contract</li>
<li>- Free healthcare insurance for you and your family</li>
<li>- Annual variable bonus if you achieve your objectives, quaterly bonus & annual bonus depending on the results of the company and medical teleconsultation.</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-german-in-porto-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in German and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the German-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in German; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales Advisor with Hungarian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/sales-advisor-with-hungarian-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>As a Sales Advisor, you will identify and cultivate new business opportunities, consult with clients to understand their needs, and provide tailored solutions to drive growth while achieving sales targets.</p>
<h3>Your responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Daily communication with new and existing clients (agencies or advertisers) via phone, chat, and email to identify sales opportunities and offer solutions tailored to their business goals.</li>
<li>- Consultative selling to better understand clients' needs and help them achieve their objectives.</li>
<li>- Planning actions based on clients needs and expectations.</li>
<li>- Researching industries and business models to better understand markets and clients.</li>
<li>- Understanding local specifics to better tailor offers for local advertisers.</li>
<li>- Providing personalized recommendations based on clients needs.</li>
<li>- Assisting clients in optimizing product usage, offering active support in problem-solving and performance improvement.</li>
<li>- Expanding knowledge of advertising solutions and their impact on business performance.</li>
<li>- Solving problems, identifying trends, and providing valuable feedback on products.</li>
<li>- Using various tools to communicate effectively and help clients succeed.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Employer requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Hungarian.</li>
<li>- Communicative English (at least B2 level).</li>
<li>- Previous experience in sales and/or marketing is preferred.</li>
<li>- Strong verbal and written communication skills.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Opportunity to advance your career within an international and multicultural environment.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance coverage from your first day.</li>
<li>- Extensive training, plus dedicated coaches to support personal and professional growth.</li>
<li>- A clear path for growth and development within the organization, with support from a highly collaborative team.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Service Agent - Banking Company with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-service-agent-banking-company-with-german-in-porto-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in German and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Porto! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in German B2</li>
<li>- Fluent, verbal and written skills in English (C1);</li>
<li>- Excellent communication skills;</li>
<li>- Strong phone contact handling skills and active listening;</li>
<li>- Customer orientation and ability to adapt/respond to different types of characters.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Porto for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enfermeiros/as - Recrutamento para a Bélgica]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/enfermeiros-as-para-belgica-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Estamos a recrutar enfermeiros/as para o nosso cliente, uma rede de hospitais e clínicas de renome na Bélgica. Procuramos profissionais qualificados e motivados para integrar equipas dinâmicas, com excelentes condições de trabalho.</p>
<h3>Detalhes da Oferta:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Salário: 2.450 euros líquidos mensais para recém-licenciados.</li>
<li>- Remuneração ajustada à experiência profissional.</li>
<li>- Contrato: Sem termo (permanente).</li>
<li>- Início: Trabalho como enfermeiro/a desde o primeiro dia.</li>
<li>- Progressão: Aumentos salariais anuais automáticos, alinhados com a taxa de inflação.</li>
<li>- Oportunidades de progressão na carreira.</li>
<li>- Financiamento de especializações e pós-graduações pelos hospitais.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefícios Adicionais:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Dois bónus anuais.</li>
<li>- Equilíbrio entre vida pessoal e profissional.</li>
<li>- Apoio: Assistência completa na documentação, processos burocráticos e recolocação na Bélgica (apoio na procura de casa)</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requisitos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Formação em Enfermagem reconhecida na União Europeia.</li>
<li>- Nível de francês B1 (obrigatório).</li>
<li>- Motivação para trabalhar na Bélgica.</li>
</ul>
<p>Está a dar o seu consentimento, ao abrigo do RGPD, para que os detalhes do seu CV sejam partilhados diretamente com o nosso cliente para fins de recrutamento.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-with-german-in-szczecin-pl]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in German and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Szczecin! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>Your Mission:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide customer service support and resolve routine issues related to banking products and services.</li>
<li>- Help customers with their financial challenges and find quick, efficient solutions.</li>
<li>- Deliver top-quality service and build positive customer experiences.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with your team to make each day a success.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We’re Looking For:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- German speaker – B2+/C1 level</li>
<li>- Strong communication and problem-solving skills.</li>
<li>- Passion for teamwork and learning.</li>
<li>- Customer-oriented mindset, especially in the financial sector.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Salary: 7,900 PLN gross/month.</li>
<li>- Contract Type: Labour contract (UoP) – stable and fully protected by Polish Labour Law.</li>
<li>- Benefits: LuxMed, MultiSport, MyBenefit cafeteria, and more!</li>
<li>- Working hours: Full time, different shifts with following the time frame - Mon-Sun 09:00- -18:00-CET.</li>
<li>- Work Model: Onsite in Szczecin.</li>
<li>- Growth opportunities in the banking industry with top-tier training provided.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Services Officer with French]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-services-officer-with-french-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Our client is currently seeking new Client Services Officer on a permanent contract to join them and help meet the challenges of our growth.</p>
<p>This position is based at our Lisbon office, where you will become part of a dynamic and supportive management team.</p>
<p>In this role, you will advise and assist our clients with their inquiries via phone and email.</p>
<p>Are you fluent in French and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Handle customer inquiries and provide advice regarding their health insurance contracts, coverage, reimbursements, and all aspects of their contract life (subscription, amendments, cancellations, premiums, etc.).</li>
<li>- Contracts: registration and cancellation, premium collection.</li>
<li>- Health services: enter reimbursements, create quotes, issue coverage approvals... in accordance with internal procedures.</li>
<li>- Client files: update and modify customer records (contract details, address, bank account information, etc.).</li>
<li>- Contribute to customer satisfaction through the quality of your responses, the efficiency of your work, and your contribution to achieving performance indicators.</li>
<li>- There will be no sales or prospecting involved in this role.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in French</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Permanent contract</li>
<li>- Free healthcare insurance for you and your family</li>
<li>- Annual variable bonus if you achieve your objectives, quarterly bonus & annual bonus depending on the results of the company and medical teleconsultation.</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beauty Advisor with Greek]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/beauty-advisor-with-greek-in-porto-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Porto!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team.</p>
<p>We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential.</p>
<p>Are you fluent in Greek and passionate about beauty? Represent a luxury brand in Customer Care – this opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide advice, answer questions, and promote the client’s brands in every interaction;</li>
<li>- Communicate with consumers by telephone, email, live chat, messaging and social media;</li>
<li>- Provide advanced sales through servicing to ensure well rounded and complete beauty solution for consumers;</li>
<li>- Place orders, resolve technical queries, and undertake associated administrative activities.</li>
<li>- Provide first contact resolution on service inquiries, complaints and on complex consumer questions within a variety of topics;</li>
<li>- Liaise with leadership and other teams to ensure a full resolution for the consumer.</li>
<li>- Understand the potential risk to the business of some inquiries/complaints; Show awareness when cases need to be escalated to an I&E advisor or Team Leader (i.e. viral social media public posts)</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluent level of written and verbal communication skills in Greek.</li>
<li>- Good level of written and verbal communication skills in English (minimum B2).</li>
<li>- Excellent communication skills and social intelligence – empathy, self-awareness, cultural sensitivity.</li>
<li>- Aptitude for problem-solving;</li>
<li>- Dynamism and team spirit;</li>
<li>- Flexible and quick learner, able to adapt continuously.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Porto for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beauty Advisor with Italian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/beauty-advisor-with-italian-in-porto-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Porto!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team.</p>
<p>We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential.</p>
<p>Are you fluent in Italian and passionate about beauty? Represent a luxury brand in Customer Care – this opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide advice, answer questions, and promote the client’s brands in every interaction;</li>
<li>- Communicate with consumers by telephone, email, live chat, messaging and social media;</li>
<li>- Provide advanced sales through servicing to ensure well rounded and complete beauty solution for consumers;</li>
<li>- Place orders, resolve technical queries, and undertake associated administrative activities.</li>
<li>- Provide first contact resolution on service inquiries, complaints and on complex consumer questions within a variety of topics;</li>
<li>- Liaise with leadership and other teams to ensure a full resolution for the consumer.</li>
<li>- Understand the potential risk to the business of some inquiries/complaints; Show awareness when cases need to be escalated to an I&E advisor or Team Leader (i.e. viral social media public posts)</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluent level of written and verbal communication skills in Italian.</li>
<li>- Good level of written and verbal communication skills in English (minimum B2).</li>
<li>- Excellent communication skills and social intelligence – empathy, self-awareness, cultural sensitivity.</li>
<li>- Aptitude for problem-solving;</li>
<li>- Dynamism and team spirit;</li>
<li>- Flexible and quick learner, able to adapt continuously.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Porto for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Turkish - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-turkish-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Turkish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Portugal - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Turkish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apoio ao Cliente com Alemão - Remoto]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/apoio-ao-cliente-com-alemao-remoto-em-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Local de trabalho: Portugal</p>
<p>É fluente em Alemão e tem fortes competências de comunicação? Temos oportunidades de emprego entusiasmantes em Portugal! Dê o próximo passo na sua carreira ao trabalhar com algumas das principais marcas globais.</p>
<h3>O que irá fazer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comunicar com clientes por telefone, chat e email;</li>
<li>- Monitorizar e resolver casos de forma eficiente, garantindo uma rápida resolução;</li>
<li>- Assegurar a satisfação dos clientes, representando uma marca de prestígio;</li>
<li>- Desenvolver e manter relações sólidas e profissionais com parceiros, demonstrando sempre empatia;</li>
<li>- Trabalhar para alcançar os objetivos definidos pelo cliente e pela empresa.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que procuramos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluência em Alemão;</li>
<li>- Fortes capacidades de comunicação, relacionamento interpessoal e resolução de problemas;</li>
<li>- Conhecimentos básicos de informática e competências técnicas;</li>
<li>- Capacidade de multitarefa;</li>
<li>- Espírito de equipa e capacidade de prosperar num ambiente dinâmico e enérgico.</li>
</ul>
<h3>O que oferecemos:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- 40h semanais</li>
<li>- Salário mensal competitivo;</li>
<li>- Benefícios de saúde e vários outros descontos;</li>
<li>- Formação completa ministrada por formadores certificados;</li>
<li>- Oportunidades de progressão na carreira e desenvolvimento profissional;</li>
<li>- Local de trabalho - Portugal</li>
</ul>
<p>Está a dar o seu consentimento, ao abrigo do RGPD, para que os detalhes do seu CV sejam partilhados diretamente com o nosso cliente para fins de recrutamento.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with French - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-french-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in French and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Greece! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Greece - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in French.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Greece for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support with Italian - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-with-italian-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>Are you passionate about customer service? This is your opportunity! We are looking for talented and enthusiastic individuals to join our client in Portugal!</p>
<p>We are interested in candidates who speak Italian and with an extensive Customer Service experience. If you want to work in a dynamic and multicultural environment, we want to meet you!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Italian;</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills;</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with Polish]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-polish-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in Polish?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Polish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Hebrew - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-hebrew-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Remote work - Equipment provided by the company. We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Hebrew and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Hebrew-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Hebrew; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Content Moderation with Danish]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/content-moderation-with-danish-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Danish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>As a Content Moderator, you will be responsible for reviewing and moderating content posted on social media platforms, ensuring alignment with client guidelines and community standards. This role requires a high level of cultural and language proficiency to ensure the authenticity and appropriateness of content for the Danish-speaking audience.</p>
<h3>Key Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Evaluate user-generated content to ensure adherence to platform guidelines and community standards.</li>
<li>- Stay up-to-date on all relevant policies, procedures, and community guidelines to make accurate moderation decisions.</li>
<li>- Track trends in content issues and provide feedback to improve moderation processes. Propose improvements based on observed trends and data.</li>
<li>- Utilize best practices to effectively meet and exceed client KPIs and goals.</li>
<li>- Collaborate with internal teams to share insights, suggest improvements, and contribute to the overall success of moderation projects.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Danish; English proficiency at a B2 level or above is also required.</li>
<li>- Prior experience in content moderation or related fields is preferred, especially in handling high volumes of content.</li>
<li>- Ability to objectively assess content, independent of personal beliefs.</li>
<li>- Detail-oriented with strong analytical skills to identify content nuances.</li>
<li>- Fast learner, adaptable to new tools and changing guidelines.</li>
<li>- Positive attitude and strong motivation to contribute to the team.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Benefits:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Stable employment with opportunities for career progression in a dynamic industry.</li>
<li>- Comprehensive health insurance starting from your first day.</li>
<li>- Performance-based monthly and quarterly bonuses.</li>
<li>- Access to continuous training and upskilling opportunities to support your growth within the organization.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with Hungarian]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-hungarian-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in Hungarian?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Hungarian.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-with-german-in-pomeranian-voivodeship-pl]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing.</p>
<p>Are you passionate about customer service? This is your opportunity! We are looking for talented and enthusiastic individuals to join our client in Gdansk!</p>
<p>We are interested in candidates who speak German and with an extensive Customer Service experience. If you want to work in a dynamic and multicultural environment, we want to meet you!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in German;</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills;</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Gdansk for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with German]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-german-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in German?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in German.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Spanish - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-spanish-remote-in-greece-gr]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Spanish and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in ! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in  - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Spanish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to  for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Client Support with Dutch - Remote]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/client-support-with-dutch-remote-in-portugal-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client - a worlds leading outsourcing company that provides services related to customer/technical support, content moderation, sales and marketing. Are you fluent in Dutch and have strong communication skills? We have exciting job opportunities in Portugal! Take the next step in your career by working with some of the top global brands.</p>
<p>Work from Home in Portugal - Equipment Provided by the company</p>
<p>Online training</p>
<p>Rotating hours: 40h/week</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Communicate with customers via phone, chat, and email.</li>
<li>- Monitor and resolve cases efficiently to ensure quick resolution.</li>
<li>- Maintain customer satisfaction while representing a major brand.</li>
<li>- Develop and sustain strong, professional relationships with partners, always showing empathy.</li>
<li>- Work towards achieving targets set by both the client and the company.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Dutch.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Portugal for candidates relocating from abroad;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment.</p>]]></description>
        </item>  
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support for Social Media with Danish]]></title>
            <link><![CDATA[https://recruityard.com/find-jobs-all/customer-support-for-social-media-with-danish-in-lisbon-pt]]></link>  
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We are recruiting on behalf of our client, a leading outsourcing company providing customer and technical support, content moderation, sales, and marketing services. We have exciting job opportunities in Lisbon!</p>
<p>Take the next step in your career by working with top global brands in a dynamic, fast-paced environment alongside a supportive team. We seek individuals eager to make an impact, add value, and unleash their full potential. Are you fluent in Danish?  This opportunity is for you!</p>
<h3>What You Will Do:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Provide support to high level clients to help them grow across multiple channels – chat, email and phone;</li>
<li>- Support and expand the self-serve advertising base for clients in the online and digital advertising domain;</li>
<li>- As a Customer Delight for Social Media, you’ll provide pre and post-sales support for all self-service products;</li>
<li>- Provide product and tool support to enhance clients’ experience;</li>
<li>- Identify and solve problems, such as technical bugs and ads’ delivery issues;</li>
<li>- Resolve customer issues in a timely manner and pro-actively communicate to clients on progress;</li>
<li>- Pro-actively identify areas where clients can improve usage of our solutions;</li>
<li>- Provide vital product insights and feedback from our customers to engineering.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What You Need:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Fluency in Danish.</li>
<li>- Proficient English communication skills.</li>
<li>- Strong communication, interpersonal, and problem-solving abilities;</li>
<li>- Basic computer knowledge and technical skills;</li>
<li>- Ability to multitask effectively;</li>
<li>- Team-oriented with the ability to thrive in a fast-paced, energetic environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Offer:</h3>
<ul>
<li>- Comprehensive relocation support to Lisbon for candidates relocating within Europe;</li>
<li>- Competitive monthly salary;</li>
<li>- Health benefits and various other discounts;</li>
<li>- Full training provided by certified instructors;</li>
<li>- Opportunities for career advancement and professional development;</li>
</ul>
<p>You are giving your GDPR consent for your CV details to be shared directly with our client for the purpose of recruitment</p>]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>